[
  {"question": "معنى Apple؟", "answer": "تفاح"},
  {"question": "معنى Book؟", "answer": "كتاب"},
  {"question": "معنى Car؟", "answer": "سيارة"},
  {"question": "معنى Pen؟", "answer": "قلم"},
  {"question": "معنى Chair؟", "answer": "كرسي"},
  {"question": "معنى Table؟", "answer": "طاولة"},
  {"question": "معنى Door؟", "answer": "باب"},
  {"question": "معنى Window؟", "answer": "نافذة"},
  {"question": "معنى Sun؟", "answer": "شمس"},
  {"question": "معنى Moon؟", "answer": "قمر"}
]
